The viewers I know are aware that the prayer today will cover them until next Sunday.
What a mighty grace.
Each day you wake up and tune to Emmanuel TV, the prayer you receive is now -
(Amen.)
tomorrow - now;
on Tuesday - now;
(Amen.)
Wednesday - now;
Thursday - now;
Friday - now;
Saturday - now.
That is the prayer we are offering now.
The grace is mighty.
We asked God and He released the grace.
Viewers all over the world, those under the influence of my voice,
it is time to combat demons and whatever situation you are in – setback, affliction;
it is time to combat demons and that situation with the Word.
(Amen.)
Remember, the Word is the sword of the recreated spirit.
We walk by faith.
We require no evidence of the senses.
We have proof that the things which we are praying for have come.
(Amen.)
Take note of that.
I will not come here to pray for you if I don’t know what I am going to pray for or what we are going to recieve.
Already, the things we are about to pray for have come – healing, blessing, victory, deliverance - they have come.
(Amen!)
What a God we serve.
I will not come out and begin to pray when I don’t know God's will, when I don't know God's intention,
when I don't know God's promise - that is in vain.
I know before coming to pray that what we are about to pray for, the things we are about to pray for have come.
(Amen.)
Tell your neighbour viewers, the things we are about to pray for have come -
healing, deliverance, blessing, victory have come.
Yes.
That is why I can come out and pray.
I pray according to His will.
All you need now is to use your faith to receive them.
Faith does not originate from you and it does not originate from me.
It did not even originate from the apostles.
Faith originates from God.
We have faith.
Our faith increases because God possesses a nature.
I want to pray for you.
Receive the faith which God is prepared to give.
(Amen!)
This reminds me of what the demon-possessed boy's father said to Jesus,
"I believe, help my unbelief".
Receive the faith which God is prepared to give, in the mighty name of Jesus!
(Amen!)
Thank You, Lord!
Receive the faith which God is prepared to give you, in the name of Jesus!
Yes, thank You, Lord.
Whatever wall between you and God, be removed in the name of Jesus!
(Amen!)
When there is a wall between you and God; how will you receive blessings?
He sent forth His Word and healed them.
He sent forth His Word and delivered them.
I command deliverance on you – be delivered, in the name of Jesus!
(Amen!)
Whatever wall, hindrance – wall could be your weakness, shortcoming, limitation, sin -
whatever wall between you and God, be removed, in the name of Jesus!
Viewers, begin to confess that hindrance between you and God.
In the mighty name of Jesus, that wall, be removed!
that wall, be removed!
Yes - that wall, be removed.
That weakness, be removed.
That sin, be removed!
That limitation, be removed!
That wall, be removed, in Jesus Christ's name!
Yes.
The wall has been removed!
Let there be a relationship!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
I hear someone say, " I sense the presence of God!"
Awesome!
I feel the presence of God.
I sense the presence of God.
Awesome!
His presence overwhelms, saturates me.
What a God I am serving.
I can feel His presence.
Let there be relationship!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
In Jesus Christ's name!
Yes.
I can sense the presence of God more than ever before.
I can feel the presence of God.
Oh my God.
Confess this.
In Jesus Christ's name we pray.
(Amen.)
Now, as you know Jesus’ name, be lifted up!
Now, as you know Jesus’ name, be set on high!
As you know Jesus’ name, be delivered, in the name of Jesus!
Yes.
As you seek God, be fulfilled!
Find fulfilment as you seek God!
Find fulfilment as you seek Him!
In Jesus' name!
(Amen.)
Viewers, are you on the sick bed?
Right now, dry bones shall rise again!
I speak healing to that pain!
Healing to that affliction!
Deliverance!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus’ Name
Whatever situation you are in, be it on the sickbed, wherever it is located -
affliction in your bones, kidneys, liver, blood, muscles, tendons, fluids,
I speak deliverance, in the name of Jesus to your organs and faculties!
I command deliverance, in the name of Jesus!
Healing, in the name of Jesus!
You can begin to place your hand, wherever there is sickness, pain, affliction.
Begin to place your hand to help your faith.
You pain, affliction, don’t be stubborn!
Don’t be stubborn!
In the name of Jesus, don’t be stubborn!
Quit!
Wherever affliction is located in your organs -
affliction, don’t be stubborn!
In the name of Jesus, quit!
Quit!
In Jesus' name.
You must quit – leave!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus’ Name
In the name of Jesus!
(Amen.)
I cover you with the blood of Jesus!
Be covered by the blood of Jesus!
In Jesus Christ's name!
I can hear healing, deliverance, blessing, breakthrough!
Breakthrough!
In Jesus' name!
Thank you!